{
    "subject": "resource/Newton_Running",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Newton Running",
    "human_readable": "The name of Newton Running is Newton Running.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9554505944252014,
            "question": "What is the name of Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6702461838722229,
            "question": "Are there any famous athletes associated with Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5683816075325012,
            "question": "Is Newton Running a company or a product?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4585633873939514,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any recent news or developments related to Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4512377083301544,
            "question": "Do you know anything about the history of Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41886183619499207,
            "question": "What kind of products or services might Newton Running offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3896825313568115,
            "question": "What are some popular running shoe brands besides Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3888019919395447,
            "question": "Where might one find products from Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37697461247444153,
            "question": "What is the target market for Newton Running products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3698130249977112,
            "question": "How does Newton Running compare to other running shoe brands in terms of performance or technology?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Newton Running is Newton Running.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4694_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the target market for Newton Running products?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4694_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one find products from Newton Running?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4694_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular running shoe brands besides Newton Running?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4694_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4694_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple is \"The name of Newton Running is Newton Running.\"\n\nUpon reviewing the context information, I find that all documents mention that the brand name of Newton Running is indeed \"Newton Running\".\n\nTherefore, my response in JSON format is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The name of Newton Running is Newton Running\" is supported by all the provided documents, which consistently refer to the brand as \"Newton Running.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}